He is 13 years old and in the first year of junior high school. Favorite food?
Kamonboko.
My name is Rikako Sasaki. Pleased to meet you.
Do you have any plans you want to do in the future for Halo! Do you have any plans you would like to do in the future?
I would like to have various confrontations between the 2nd, 3rd and 3rd terms.
I would like to see it.
Since Takiuchi-san hates to lose, and I also hate to lose, I wonder what will happen?
Thank you for watching.
Hallo! Stay, this time with Rika Sasaki aka Rika Sasaki from Angeleum.
It's you, Angelem's Kamikakure.
This time I will be presenting you with these two, so please stay with me until the end.
This will be the last show before my graduation. As this is my last MC for Halo!
I started with the video of my first MC.
How did you like it?
I was a 13-year-old girl who liked fish cakes.
She was so cute!
Now I want to have a showdown with Mr. Niki!
I want to have a showdown with Mr. Niki!
What do you want to confront him about?
You didn't have a showdown after that?
No, we didn't.
You were like a naughty little girl, weren't you?
So today... the new single from Angulum has been released.
Yay!
Thank you very much.
So how about explaining the song?
Well, I'm scared... anyway, it's Angulum's new single.
It's cool.
The dancing has been getting more and more intense lately.
That's right.
Every time you release a song, you challenge yourself to dance in a way that requires a lot of energy.
Yes, I did.
I think rap is the main part of this song.
Yes, I think rapping is the main part of this song.
Narcissi, as the rumor goes, is Narcissi in the title, isn't it?
Yes.
I had an image that "narcissist" was often used in a negative way.I had the impression that the word "narcissist" was often used in a negative way.
But I am someone who has already said that I am a narcissist as a person who stands on the stage.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, but I consider it my weapon.
That's why when I saw the lyrics to this song...
That's right, that's what it means.
You don't have to live your life thinking you're a narcissist.
I hope you love yourself that much
Yes, yes, yes.
That's what I think.
Listen to this song and give a little pat on the back.
Yes, yes.
I thought, "Let's try to love ourselves.
Like that.
I think there are lyrics that make you take a step forward.
I understand.
Okay, the third song.
Okay.
How about "Thank you hello goodbye"?
I don't know... it's like I'm graduating.
Yes, it is.
It's a song.
But you think the day will come when you'll be able to sing this kind of song?
Yes.
It's a feeling.
But Takuya Nakajima wrote the music for this song.
It's wonderful.
I made my debut as a member of Angelem with a song written by Takuya Nakajima.
I think it's very meaningful to be covered by Takuya's song, so I was very happy.
The song and the mv are both very cute, so please watch them!
Please watch it!
Please take a look at this video.
Please enjoy!
Enjoy!
rr
movie
Before you get hurt, it's as if the future isn't spelled out.
Order light, a new road, a mouthful of imagination, I won't let you ride it.
my eyes hit the floor after the fall, mazel tov not to show it
I'll sacrifice myself in the morning and push forward to the top of the heap
I'll only go if I come back someday I'll give it my all I'll see you again I'm already on my way
Now my heart is clear, echoing the bible, embracing even the pain and darkness
I'm not talking to you.
I'm the one who gets what he wants.
Don't go numb.
I will love you.
Active Freeze
I'm tangy with time
Hot Flavor
Four Seasons Five Days Stamp Free
Audio Dorfxeimer
In the chosen hospital
They say some are chosen
When you get over it, it's despair
Expect yourself, never give up
No more scraping and scraping, no more sighs
No one ever told me I was an adult
The first time
Always the year that I forgot
The map that melts away
In my hand
On my bare skin
Blame me and I blow
I'll come for you as soon as I add a note
I'll come for you soon
I fly up
One more timeOne more time
All you guys
I fly up
A mission to take you
Not yet.
I'm not the same as I was before, but even my whole body will change
Any place I feel at home
Beyond the end, the days when I believed
I still only think of you
I'll tell someone about them
No matter the absurdity, no matter the path
No switching, overwhelming love
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Karakara bibiru hit me, make me crazy
I love you so much I'm getting tired of you
First time it changes, get it all
Once it's carved, the diamonds can be erased
One after the other, one after the other, one after the other, one after the other
I'm going through the trials and tribulations
I'm trying so hard I can't do it I'm trying so hard I'm trying so hard I'm trying so hard I'm trying so hard
I hope
I'm the one who smiles and forgives
Don't be afraid
I'll love you
Sadness, go with the wind
Don't let it pull you away
Live and let live
Live or die, keep going. Burn up.
Be right. Be right.
I don't care if this is the past or not.
I'm on your side. Let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm gonna give you the blow of your life.
I'm gonna love you.
The launch event at Club Chit is over.
How was Wakami?
Yes, I performed "Vivitar Ichibu" on that spring tour.
But I was wearing an ear monitor, so I had never heard the fans' calls before.
So I was very happy to hear the fans' cheers from close by today.I was so happy to hear the cheers of the fans up close today.
Yes, it was a new experience for me.
So how was Kero?
Yes, I did. I had been sitting up for a year, and I'm getting better, so I was finally able to join the dance.
Welcome back.
I am glad to be back, and I really enjoyed being able to feel the excitement of the fans up close as well. Thank you very much.
Yes, it was great. How about you, Mr. Sasaki?
Yes, for me, there is one more event to go.
I have one more release event at Club Chit,
So this is the last release event at this one place?
Yes, that's right,
I performed "Rumored Poem" and "Thank you, Hello, Goodbye" for the first time.
I was very nervous, but
I was very nervous, but I was happy to be able to share these wonderful songs with you all.
I'm so happy that I was able to share these wonderful songs with you all, and I'm glad that we were able to have a good time together today as well.
I am really happy. Thank you very much.
Yes, that's right, Angulum's new single, "Vivitar," "Ichigeki," "Rumor of a Rumor," "T hank you, Hello, Goodbye," and "T hank you, Hello, Goodbye" are all three songs!
There are 3 songs!
Please listen to them!
That's all for Angulum!
Let's do our best again tomorrow!
This is Rika Sasaki aka Rika Sasaki from Angelem
This is Hallo! stay!
From here, I would like to tell you a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer them in a quick tempo without thinking too much.
I understand.
The spring tour ended on June 1.
What's the first thing that comes to mind when you look back on this tour?
A moment.
New single "Vivitar Ichigeki
What is the key point of today's eyebrow drawing in reference to the
The lyrics.
You can't see it today, but I went with brown.
It's so cute!
Rikamiko 2 at the Funk Live event last month.
What did you think of the day that we haven't talked about yet?Here are some thoughts on the day that we haven't talked about yet
Mantis is the best!
What's for breakfast today?
Suddenly dumplings!
June 22nd.
What is the best way to add eyebrows?
It has been a full year since you became the third leader of Angelum.
What have you done consciously as a leader over the past year?
Talking to everyone.
It's great!
That's great!
Rikamiko2's Comments
What is the best mantis?
Do you remember?
Yes, I remember.
It was in the "What's in the box?" section.
There was a big praying mantis in the box.
It was a toy.
Before I guessed, I did this.
What is it?
What is it? I didn't know.
I didn't know.
But there was a staff member
I couldn't figure it out, but there was a staff member
Jiggle jiggle jiggle jiggle
and moved the praying mantis toy as hard as he could.
The probability of that is incredible, isn't it?
It was just a hand.
I mean, I know it's a long shot, but...
All I could see was her hand.
It was more fun than Rikamiko's.
If you ask me what I remember...
The expression on the staff's face as they worked hard to move the praying mantis.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you very much.
That was fun, wasn't it?That was fun.
And it's been a whole year since I became the third leader.
One year.
What did I say I've been doing consciously?
I've been trying to have a conversation with everyone.
I've definitely done that.
As a whole.
And I went out to dinner with each one of them.
I tried to communicate with them.
God has always been a communicator.
But I could see that he was doing it consciously.
I can see it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I know what he's doing.
I knew this was God's way of doing things.
I've been watching over you.
Thank you very much.
Questions for Mr. Sasaki after the VTR
Hello! Ste.
Revitalize Ichigiri, make him go crazy.
Make him go crazy as soon as you open the knife door.
I've never seen anything like this before... until the end.
Angulum Birital Ichigiri Now on sale
Angulum Rumors of Narcissi Now on sale
Angulum Senhee Hello Goodbye Now on sale
Haloste
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Sasaki some questions.
Last week, the graduation commemorative photobook Hirasol was released.
What was the point of this work that you stuck to anyway?
10,000 word interview
The moment when you felt the happiest in the recent universe from the lyrics of "Rumor of Narcissi" is
Yesterday
Three years ago now, I was an exclusive model for CanCan.
What does modeling mean to you?
Expression A place where you can find a different you again
What is the key to today's fashion?Today's fashion points are
T-shirt
Angstrom Concert 2024 Secret Secret
One week until Rikako Sasaki Final World of Affection, Come Here, You Too!
How do you want to spend your time?
I want to master everyday life.
I want to be the best at everyday life.
Oh!
I want you to follow all of this.
I want you to talk about all of them.
Hirasol... another 10,000-word interview.
Yes, sir.
The more you turn the page, the more you'll see of me.
Of course, I'm particular about each page.
I'm very particular about what I want to do on each page, and it's a work that's filled with a lot of things I want to do.
But there is also a word that is attached to this work.
I also have words inside me that have shaped me.
If I'm going to make this photo book, my last as an idol, into a form.
I asked her to make a page for my words.
We spent hours and hours interviewing her.
That's great.
How many pages?
And then I'll make a page with the members.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
It was great.
I'm looking forward to it.
And last but not least...
Mr. Sasaki's week before the finals is to master his daily routine.
Yes, that's right.
What do you mean?
It's just a normal week.
Yes.
If I think too much about the fact that I'm graduating...
I feel a little down.
Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, it's something I've decided for myself.
That's why I want to do my best in my daily life that I've always spent.
Together with everyoneTogether with all of you.
Let's have fun!
And we'll probably rehearse the rest.
Yes, I know.
I think you're frantic every day.
Mm-hmm.
Hang in there.
Hmm...
I'm Kimiyami Natsuyaki.
I'm Saori Onoda from Tsubaki Factory.
After this, I think dexterity will be very important.
I'll do my best to be dexterous.
I'm counting on you.
So, what shall we make this time?
Today, I'd like to make gyoza (dumplings).
I love them!
I don't usually cook.
Cooking.
I'm a little clumsy, so I don't do it very often.
I'm a little nervous today.
I'm going to try my best to make it in my own way.
Isn't it a little challenging?
Yes, it is.
It feels good, doesn't it?
Atmospheric dumplings.
All at once.
What shall we start with this time?
Well, now it's time to wrap them up!
Blow by blow by blow
If you put too much on top
Maybe a little too much
It's too much!
It's a little too bold.
It's important, though.
That's what you say.
Be bold with your cooking.
Add cheese.
It adds volume.It's going to be voluminous.
And this one's spreading out horizontally now.
We should fold it here.
Like this?
Yes, like that.
From this folded position
From here.
Bring your hand a little to the left here.
Here.
There. That's it. That's it. That's it.
I got it.
You found it? I found it. Here it comes.
It's like I'm pulling it in like this. I'm not just bringing it to the top.
You have to start from the bottom. You have to start from the bottom.
First one. It's my first time doing this.
It's good, it's good, it's good.
Show it to the camera. Show it to the camera. How's it going?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
How's it going? Is it weird? How's it going?
It's weird.
It's a little bit like yatsuhashi.
But still, for a first time...
Yes, yes, yes, for a first time.
I saw it over here.
I'll show you some tricks.
You'll get the hang of it.
With the remaining five, we'll play a little game.
Game on!
Okay, practice makes perfect.
You're doing great.
But, refurbish. Beautiful, beautiful.
Repair. Let me see. Second one.
What do you think? I can see it, I can see it.
It's getting darker.
You're making great progress.
It fits. Maybe we should move it to the left.
The more you wrap it like this, the more it moves to the right.As you wrap it up like this, it moves to the right.
It's going to stick out and then it's going to be dropped.
And then it almost sticks out.
It was sticking out.
That's right.
Like this.
Yes, yes.
A little more often.
Oh, much more than the first time.
Actions.
Yes!
It's getting better.
It's still got some personality.
Yes.
It's a little different from the teacher's.
This is so good! So beautiful!
It's so good!
I'm so happy.
I'm going to get even more serious from here.
Good!
Let him do it.
That's pretty badass. Really badass.
I'm so excited.
I was actually hoping to hear a little bit about Shanghai.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I'm in serious mode.
No, no, no, no, no.
You'll talk to me.
I'll talk to you.
Talk to me.
How was the show?
Everyone who came to the show was really enthusiastic and excited about the show.
We were all a little overwhelmed!
Even before the show, I was so excited because Marin Fukuda was born in Shanghai!
I have a picture of her...
Here it is!Yes, sir.
I mean, it's a triumph.
That's great.
It started with a call of "Ma Lin.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
That name is also in Chinese.
They called out the name "Ma Lin" in Chinese.
We were so excited before the show.
And during the show, everyone held up the same towel as a surprise for us...
It was so nice!
It was my first time in Shanghai.
It's my first time.
Oh, right.
So everything I saw was new to me.
It was a fresh feeling.
But I also felt relieved to be able to go with the members for the first time.
Yes, that's for sure.
I had a lot of fun.
I would like to do my best so that we can go more regularly.
That's great.
Last one.
All right.
The culmination.
That's right.
Just concentrate on the last one.
Okay.
Isn't this fun?
It's fun.
I don't mind.
If you do it quickly...
You can do it all the time?
Yes, I can.
I don't know.
Oh, my God.
So many.
They're all beautiful, aren't they?
They're beautiful.
Let's call it a tie.Can we call it a tie now?
Can we call it a draw?
But it's really a tie, and it's beautiful.
Attachment?
Good, good, good.
They're cute, aren't they?
This is Honda and this is Sensei.
You're so good!
Yay!
They said it's a tie, so it's a tie.
Now, let's bake the dumplings, teacher.
Yes, now it's time to bake them.
Please do.
Just put them on the pan.
If you put them on too flat, they will stick together too much.
I don't know.
It's like a big splash of water, like a "bouchang" or a "chew".
You know, it is better to put hot water instead of water.
That's right.
If you don't use hot water, the water will cool down the pan.
If you put water in, the skin will cool down, so the skin will become a little squishy, and you won't be able to make it crispy.
Thank you very much.
That is Miyamizu's point.
I've said it all.
I said it all.
Yes, hot water is added when baking.
That's funny.
You're a funny guy, too.
Wait a minute.
It's going to be a little bit hot.
Wait a minute, will it?
Oh, really.
Oh!
Do you want to steam it with this? Yes.
If you do it with water, it won't turn out like this. It would go into a constant warp, but with a single sink.
If you do it like this from the beginning, it will be boiling.
When the water runs out, it gets burnt, so you have to add more water,If the water runs out, it will burn, so you will have to add more water,
As a rule of thumb, the skin should be translucent, but I think it will be OK.
Also, I heard that the "winged" type is very popular. Can you do that?
I can do it, but I don't want to overdo it today.
If you put a little potato starch or flour in the hot water, it will remain.
So there's a way to make it. Wow, it looks good. Looks delicious!
And it's all stuck together. The top is not open. It's not open. I'm so happy. That's good.
It's coming back down. This is the important part. Weaken it a bit.
Is it still losing moisture? The spray.
Is the moisture gone? Spraying.
A little bit of oil, a little bit of oil.
From this side, too. Yes, gently.
Then, turn the frying pan at an angle to the other side.
This is how you get a nice browning.
Be careful.
Ta-da!
Wow!
So beautiful! Amazing! Amazing! Looks delicious!
That's great. Yeah!
Look at this! It's done!
Yay! I'm so happy! Looks delicious!
The dumplings are done!
Yay!
What do you think?
Well, it looks really delicious from the outside,
And now that it's right here in front of me, I can already smell it,
It smells so good!
It smells so good, I'm so hungry, I can't wait to eat it.
I can't wait to eat it. Please do eat it.
By the way, what kind of sauce do you have this time?
Yes, I did. The sauce is a combination of your favorite oyster soy sauce and sesame oil.
This is the combination.
It's an iron plate.
Here you go. Here you go.
Please eat it right away.
Yes. Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
Bon appétit.Bon appétit.
Yum!
Yuck! Yummmmmm!
Wow, it's delicious!
It's so good!
That was so good!
What is it? The flower beds are so sticky.
The cabbage is so crispy and delicious!
Please eat it slowly.
Thank you so much!
I think some of you may make this recipe with this as a reference.
It's really easy to make, so I hope you make a lot of them!
Above all, it's delicious!
If you look at it, you can see how doughy and sticky it is!
Hot water is very important!
If you use water, it might not be as moist.
You have to take care of the points.
Please try to take care of the points!
Please come to Hello Kitchen again!
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen!
Bye bye!
This is Haloste, with Rikako Sasaki and Ryumoe Kamikuro from Angulum.
Next week on June 19th at Yokohama Arena, Angulum Concert 2024 Secret Secret
Rikako Sasaki's final performance, "Come to the World of Love, Come to You" will be held on June 19th.
Yes, that's right, this time I'd like to ask Ms. Sasaki a few questions about her graduation.
Please do.
Please do. Okay, let's get started.
Okay, let's get started.
You've been a member of Angstrom for about 10 years.
Yes, 10 years.
So, Ms. Sasaki, when do you think was the turning point in your career?
The one that comes to mind for me is the 10 member Twilo tour in 2018.
The tour before that was probably the one that changed and stayed the same.
It's amazing to see what's changed since then.
It's quite different.
Even for me.
But it's still in my mind.But there was still a time when I was not satisfied with my performance.
I was not satisfied with my performance
I think I was 16 years old
I was 16 years old.
The final performance was at the Budokan.
The final performance was at Budokan, and it was titled "10 People's Toilo Plus Final".
I turned 17 on that day.
I remember that day.
Yes, the Budokan was all yellow.
Rikako's call was heard.
I was really happy.
I remember that I was really happy.
I remember that tour was very memorable for me, and I think it's burned in your memories too.
It was such a memorable tour that I think it is still burned in your memories as well.
I think I changed a lot on that tour.
Then, there is a question about what kind of a presence the 3rd term member Sasaki-san was to me, the only 4th term member...
That's true.
That's right.
I was the only one who joined the tour in the beginning, and you were also a senior member, Wada san, so we all had a lot of colleagues...
Yes, there were.
Wada san was on her own after Fukuda san graduated, but she and Niki san and Smileage had a strong bond.
That's right.
I was the only one who joined the group, so at that time, Mr. Sasaki was very supportive of me, as was Mr. Sasaki, and Mr. Miki.
And Mr. Miki, since there were three of us, it was an odd number, so there was always one person below me.
It was Mr. Sasaki at that time.
That's right.
When we were in a room together at a hotel, I was often in the room with Mr. Sasaki because he was one of the three and there was not much room for us.
So when I look at old photos, there are a lot of pictures of us having fun and joking around at the hotel.
It brings back memories.
Yes, yes.
But I think that's how our bond with Mr. Miki became so strong.
God has been calling me "Mr. Miki, Mr. Miki" for a long time.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I was like, "He's just a cute junior.
But then I realized that she was always by my side.
We're senior and junior again.
But I feel like we have a different kind of relationship.
That's exactly what I felt when Clio Kamiko and Moe-chan joined the group.That's exactly when Kamiko Clio Moe-chan joined the group.
I was just in junior high school.
That's right, I was in the eighth grade.
I was in the eighth grade.
But I was in the rebellious phase
It was my rebellious period.
I called my mother.
And she's sitting next to me, smiling at me.
She was like, "Mr. Sasaki, you're doing it again.
I thought it was kind of cute.
I really thought so.
She seemed to think so.
He's such a grouch.
I thought it was cute that she thought that about me.
I was really happy.
I know it's not where my heart is, but...
But I'll always love you.
Haloste
Haloste.
Okay, so up until now I've been asking you a lot of questions looking back on the past.
When was the moment when you started to realize that you were going to graduate or step up to the next level?
I don't really have a big trigger.
I guess it was just an accumulation of things.
I like to express myself.
I like to see and show myself in different ways.
I want to see myself differently.
I want to be tossed about by various waves.
When my desire came to me in a flash
Graduation was something I couldn't imagine
But this feeling of graduation that popped up somewhere in my mind
I thought that it was probably real.
That's right.
I told her as it was.
I guess that's how I feel.
It's nostalgic.
I miss it.I miss it.
I've been going around and around about whether this is the right thing to do or not.
I've been thinking about graduation over and over again.
I've never had the courage to take the first step toward graduation.
I've been avoiding it, thinking that maybe this is the only time I'm feeling this way.
I've been avoiding it because I thought it might be the only time.
I had a moment when I knew it was the right time.
That's when I made my decision.
That's really cool.
It's hard to make a decision, so...
That's right.
When you live your life, you have to make choices all the time.
But making a choice takes a lot of courage, and it's scary.
And it makes you want to run away.
But in the end, it's all right because I chose it.
I believe that.
That's what I think.
I don't regret my choice.
I've heard a lot of your stories.
Lastly, I would like to say a few words to the fans
To the audience
Please give a message to those who came to the graduation performance.
To all of you who have loved me so much
Thank you so much for loving me so much.
I have been a member of Halo Project for about 11 years.
I've been a member of Halo Project for about 11 years.
But as I said before...
I was just saying that...
I also talked about many other things.
The things that shape me
One of the things that have supported me
The existence of all of you...
Yes, all of you fans...
All the viewers.
And everyone who came to the graduation performance.
I am truly surrounded by
everyone in my environmentEveryone in the environment
Really, everyone.
Everyone.
You.
Yes, you.
I'm bringing it to you.
Really, uh...
Many, many, many thanks.
Thank you so much.
I can't thank you enough.
I don't know...
And the view, too.
I got so many things from you all.
I've received so many things from all of you.
I don't know how to put it into words.
And when I put it into words
I think it's a waste of time.
I think it's a waste.
I think it's a waste of my
But inside of me, it's like a treasure
In my heart
Inside me
I'm holding on to it
I keep it in my heart.
I'm going to use the warmth
I will continue to use the warmth
As strength
I hope I can live
I hope to be able to live
And the same goes for my customers.
I am you.
I hope I can be of help to you.
I'd be happy if I could be of help to you.
If you'd like, I can continue to be that way.
I'd like to be...
I would like to beI'd like to be there.
If you have time, that's fine.
I hope you don't forget about me.
I want you to look at me.
I'd like you to look at me.
There's only a week left until graduation.
I know it's only a week, but it's still a week.
So you have seven days.
During that time, I'll be
As Rikako Sasaki
I will live my life to the fullest.
Thank you all for your cooperation until the very end.
Thank you very much.
We're here!
Shanhammariya.
What's a marine marine?
Marin-marin.
Marine Marine.
So cute!
My illustration is so cute!
Garlic
We've arrived at Montpactree Shanghai!
Yay!
Very hot
So hot!
It's an event concept for tomorrow.
We're excited too, so
We're going to do our best and enjoy the sheer fun!
It's going to be fun!
Thank you for watching!
Ending.
We're about to start the CanHigh performance.
I put on a ponytail today to get into the spirit of the show.
I don't often wear a ponytail at live performances.
I only have 6 more shows left.After all, I only have six more gigs left!
When I think about it...
What? But I still want to have fun and show various aspects of myself.
But I still want to have fun and show different sides of myself.
I decided to do my hair in a way that I usually don't do with my friends.
I also thought about the last time I went on an overseas call.
I felt that the way to enjoy live performance is different from Japan.
I felt that the way to enjoy live performance was different from Japan, in a good way.
The same goes for the calls.
I also felt that the way to enjoy and enjoy the live performance was totally different from Japan.
So I'm quite excited about today's show in Shanghai, and I wonder what the fans in Shanghai will be like.
I'm really excited to see what the fans in Shanghai will be like.
The show starts in about 10 minutes.
I'm going to enjoy the show in about 10 minutes.
Oh, I feel like I'm falling on my voice a little bit.
Oh no!
I'm nervous.
Nervous, right?
I'm a little nervous.
I'm more nervous about the MC than the performance.
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm sure all the members are going to be very nervous about the show.
What are you going to say?
It's not fun.
Kwai.
Oh, it's so good!
Is she pretty?
Yes, it's cute.
Is it cute?
You say that in Chinese.
Not really, but...
Kwai.
One word I learned.
Okay, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
No, I like it underpants.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Okay, I'll go one more time.Okay, let's go one more time.
Ami, Mizuho, Saori, Kunao, Yumi, Ri, Kunao.
OK.
What should we do?
When you win, Kang-san,
This is the key type,
This is the side of the key type.
And if Mr. Kang wins,
If Mr. Kang wins,
Go to the second side,
once more, so that the speed does not change,
so that Mr. Kang will win,
Yes, let's go back.
Okay, Mr. Kang,
Let's go for it.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, let's just watch out for the rookies.
Not forgetting owing
Matsumaki Factory First Concert 2024
Come on everybody to Shanghai
Welcome everybody!
Laugh, laugh, laugh, I'm tired of laughing
I'm about to cry
Let go of your pride
I don't care if it's a gallop
Blow your horn one more time.
Stop it. You're the real deal.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
The kiramator of premonition
Before you wish... Can you rewind it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It was a dream.
May I do what I've been wanting to do ever since I entered Tsubaki no Hitori?
Yes, When I say I'm home, Can you say Welcome back?
When I say "I'm back," you say "Welcome back. I'm coming.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Welcome home.Welcome back.
Glad to be here.
Good.
Your lovely flowers arrived.
Thank you
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
I probably got a lot of love from people in the company.
I am really happy.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
If you're serious, yeah, ex-husband.
You can use words, you can use actions, you can use love, you can use all of that power.
Free me. Hold me tight.
I'll run away if you're too generous.
Kindness is not something you can get
That's why all I have is what you feel.
It's me
Back Factory's performance in Shanghai is over!
How was it, Marin, who was born in Shanghai?
I'm really happy to be able to come to the city where I grew up in my childhood with all the members.
I was so happy to be able to come to the city where I grew up, and I was so happy that the fans, including the members, surprised me before the show.
I was so happy to be able to come to the city where I grew up with all the members.
I was able to feel the love of so many people from Shanghai at the concert.
I hope we can come back to Shanghai again to perform overseas if we have a chance.
Well, Shiori!
I would like to thank all the people who came from Japan and Shanghai, as well as those who came from other places.
And those who came from other places than Shanghai.
I hope that everyone will have the
the same
Tsubaki Factory's music.
It was so fresh and fun to have the same sense of unity.
The day before the event, we took a walk around the city of Shanghai.
I was happy to know many good things about Shanghai.
I will do my best to come back to Shanghai again.
It's been 16 years since Hello! Project has not been to Shanghai in 16 years, I think.It's been 16 years since the Hello! Project hasn't been to Shanghai in 16 years, I think.
Yes, that's right.
I was very happy that we, Tsubaki Factory, would be performing for the first time in 16 years.
I hope we can come back again.
Thank you so much everyone!
Thank you very much.
That's all for Tsubaki Factory!
I hope you had a good day.
I hope he wasn't talking about you!
It's always so beautiful
I'm anxious all the time
I'll be back tomorrow
Let's go home Let's take our memories with us
Let's go home, let's see you again
La La La La La La La La
We're almost there... just one more step... fight!
This is Halo! Sta, presented by Moe Kamikuro Rei, Rika Sasaki of Angeleum.
It's time for us to say goodbye.
I'm not sure if it's our first time together or not... but we've been looking back on the first time we met, and we've heard a lot of stories about you.
I'm sure that your words are words that only you can speak, so it was a very precious time for me.
It was a very precious time for me.
I was so happy to have the opportunity to MC together with Moe, the divine black spirit, and I felt so comfortable having her next to me when I was speaking.
I wasn't nervous at all.
I was not nervous.
I always have a problem with my speech, but today I can say I had a good time.
It was fun. I was able to relax and have fun at the same time. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Today, Angulum's new single "Vivitar Ichigeki Rumonotsu no Narushi Senkyu Hello Goodbye" has been released!
I hope you listen to it a lot and check out the music video.
Please check out the music video!
And then, Angulum Concert 2024 Secret Secret!
Rikako Sasaki's final concert "Come to the World of Love" will be held on June 19th at Yokohama Arena.
I don't know how I'm going to spend my time, but I'm sure we'll all be at Yokohama Arena.
I don't know how I'm going to spend my time, but I'm sure we're all going to make it to Yokohama Arena.
I don't know how we will spend our time.
I really want to do my best for Yokohama Arena.
I think we are in the middle of working hard.I think we are in the middle of working hard on it.
I hope you are all waiting for it with great anticipation!
Thank you very much.
And this is also Ms. Sasaki's graduation commemorative photo book, isn't it?
That's right!
Rikako Sasaki's graduation commemorative photo book is now on sale!
It's filled with the cute and lovely Rikako Sasaki!
It's really packed.
Yes.
So please, everyone!
Please check it out! I'm looking forward to working with you.
Hello! Project members will be appearing more and more on this channel.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel.
Please rate, comment, and subscribe to our channel.
This time, my partner is Rika Sasaki a.k.a. Moe Kamiya of Angulum,
Moe Kamiya, a.k.a. Rika Sasaki of Angeleum, was my partner this time.
Bye bye. Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.